Finding Aid to the AIDS History Project — Ephemera Collection, 1973, 1981-2002 MSS.2000.31
University of California, San Francisco Archives & Special Collections
AIDS history project — ephemera collection
1973, 1981-2002
University of California, San Francisco Archives & Special Collections
University of California, San Francisco. Library. Archives and Special Collections
MSS.2000.31
7 Linear Feet 5 boxes, 1 takeout box, 1 map box, 9 oversize folders
This is an artificial collection assembled from a number of different donations of ephemeral materials, acquired by the Library as a part of the AIDS History Project. Paper based materials include flyers, brochures, wallet cards, and posters from the US and international sources. Some artifacts are also included, such as condoms and condom holders. All deal with the medical and/or social aspects of AIDS and HIV, with a focus on prevention and on addressing misconceptions about the disease.
General
Finding Aid Written By:
Julia Bazar
Date Completed:
May 2007
Access
Collection is open for research.
Separated Materials
Oversize materials have been stored in the flat files of the UCSF Archives and Special Collections.
Related Collections
AR 91-19 Sixth International Conference on AIDS Records
MSS 94-60 San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF) Records
MSS 98-48 Shanti Project Records
MSS 98-47 ACT-UP Golden Gate Records
MSS 2000-32 AIDS History Project Audio/Video Collection
MSS 94-59 National Task Force on AIDS Prevention Records
MSS 95-02 GAPA Community HIV Project (GCHP) Papers
MSS 95-03 Mobilization Against AIDS (MOB) Records
Acquisition Information
The materials in this collection were compiled from several donations, including MSS 94-60 San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF) Records, and other national and international organizations and individuals contacted during the AIDS History Project.
System of Arrangement
The collection is arranged to the folder level, with oversize materials arranged to the item level.
Organizational History
The UCSF AIDS History Project was started in 1987 to promote the preservation of historically significant resources relating to the early days of the AIDS Epidemic, with a particular focis on San Francisco's community-based organizations (CBOs). In 1991 a National Historical Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC) grant was received to fund the AIDS History Project Records Survey. More than 50 agencies were surveyed to identify records that should be permanently preserved. A second two-year NHPRC grant funded an extended survey of collections and development of an acquisition plan. A major part of the project was providing instruction in records management practices to the CBOs. A third two-year NHPRC grant was received in 1993 for the Records Acquisition and Processing Project (RAPP) phase; this grant lasted until December 1995.
The ephemeral materials came in several donations over the length of the project and were combined into a single artificial collection. In 2018, a number of large posters from international sources were aquired and integrated into the collection.
Scope and Content of Collection
This is an artificial collection assembled from a number of different donations of ephemeral materials, acquired by the Library as a part of the AIDS History Project. The materials consist of small items (flyers, brochures, condom holders, wallet cards) and large posters. The smaller items are arranged by theme and/or creating organization. There are two kinds of posters, those held in the map box, and oversize posters held in map sized folders, arranged on the item level. The oversize items are arranged by location and/or language found on flyer. The medium sized posters are organized by location. Paper based materials include flyers, brochures, wallet cards, and posters. Some artifacts are also included, such as condoms and condom holders. All materials address the medical and social aspects of AIDS and HIV, with a focus on prevention and addressing misconceptions about the disease.
Accruals
No future additions are expected.
AIDS (Disease); AIDS (Disease)--Social aspects; AIDS (Disease)--Prevention; Advertising, Public service; University of California San Francisco; Ephemera.; Shanti Project (San Francisco, Calif.); San Francisco AIDS Foundation
- Small items and Paper-based Ephemera, 1973; 1981-1994,; undated; Series 1; 42 Folders: Boxes 1-3
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of flyers, brochures, condom holders and safe-sex instructions, and wallet cards. The materials have been arranged alphabetically by subject, except for the first folder which contains information on other sexually-transmitted diseases, and the final five folders containing pamphlets arranged geographically and a folder of information from San Francisco Agencies not surveyed by the AIDS History Project (AHP).
  - Native-Americans, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Asian-Americans, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - African-Americans, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Latinos, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - People of Color, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AIDS and Deaf Community, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Inmates/Prisoners, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Drugs and Drug Users, 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gay Men, 1981-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Heterosexuals, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Family and Caretakers, 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Children, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Women, 1984-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - General Audience, 1983-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Workers, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Youth, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - HIV Infected, 1983-1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Historical Ephemera/ Early or otherwise significant, 1982-1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Origins/History of HIV/AIDS, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Other Sexually-Transmitted Diseases/Pre-AIDS, 1973-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Antibody Testing, 1985-1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alternative Therapies, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1983-1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Scapegoating/Hysteria, 1981-1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Quackery and Scams, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers and Clippings, 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Mainstream and Medical Magazines, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - People with AIDS – Healing Tales - KALW, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Organizations/Resources – Education, Services, etc, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco Aids Foundation, 1983-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - SFAF Duplicate Staff Minutes for Exhibit, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, 1981 June 5 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - AIDS Health Project, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - UCSF School of Nursing Faculty AIDS Conference, September 17, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Politics and Protests, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - UCSF AIDS Awareness Week, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Information from SF Agencies not Surveyed by AHP, Circa 1981 - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Condom Information: Condom Resource Center/ Other Sources, 1985-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Pamphlets on AIDS Issues and Prevention (Box 3, Folder 5-8)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis and New York, circa 1981 - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Elsewhere in the United States, circa 1981 - 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Canada, Circa 1985 - 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Outside North America, circa 1981 - 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dannemayer Initiative – Proposition 102, July-November 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Magazine Covers from 1986 - 1989, circa 1986 - 1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Posters and Oversized Items, 1981-2002; Series 2; Box 4 and Map Case: 69 items
  This series consists primarily of posters and a few oversized items (Braille version of the Surgeon General's Report), etc. Items listed from bottom of box to top.
  - Paper Bag of Pin-back Buttons (Box Box 4, Items 1)
  - AIDS and ARC - A Resource Manual - Publication, circa 1985*** (Box 4, Item 2)
  - The Complete Guide to Safe Sex - Institute for Advanced Study of Human Sexuality, 1987 (Box 4, Item 3)
  - You Can Do Something About AIDS, 1988 (Box 4, Item 4)
  - San Francisco Aids Foundation Mounted Posters on Foamcore (5), circa 1981 - 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Matted Photograph – Protest at San Francisco Federal Building – "Fighting For our Lives." Banner and 7 men, Copyright: Mick Hicks [20"x16"], 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Posters (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
    - "San Francisco AIDS Foundation Welcomes You To Gay Games II" color envelopes, [9-1/2" x 13"] (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 1-2)
      - Male Images – contains 8 assorted brochures and packet of Probe lubricant, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Female Images – empty, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - The SFAF presents "Sex in the Age of AIDS: South of Market Style" – Man's torso with dog tag, leather vest, jeans, and beer bottle – ad for a forum, b/w, [11" x 8-1/2"], Wednesday, February 29th, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - "The Ultimate Point … Shooting up and Sharing Needles Puts you at Risk for AIDS. This Fact May Save Your Life" – Red/navy on white graphic [11" x 17"], 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - "Celebrate National Condom Week … Use Condoms Stop the AIDS Virus" – Dancing Condoms, L.Stinson, [11" x17"], February 14-21 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - "AIDS Prevention … Don't Share Tattoo Kits" – Heart with "Mother" written across [11" x 17"], 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - "The More You SHOP For Life … The More You Shop For LIFE" – standup display ads, [10-3/4" x 15-1/2"] (2 copies), Saturday, November 25th, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - "Exhibit Guide" – two sided, Text and graphic on front, text and photographs on back – mounted on cardboard – installation Time Capsule, San Francisco Public Library, date from t-shirt on graphic [10-3/4" x 17"], 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - "Laff 'n' Bowl" – Comedy and Bowling fundraiser for SFAF, from Autumn Press, Sunday, November 29th, circa 1987 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - "Dress for the Occasion" – Naked man wearing condom (3 copies) [15" x 19-3/4"], 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 9 - 11)
    - "There's a time to talk. There's a time to play. There's a time to talk about play" – Three naked men except for boots and leather paraphernalia, One man putting condom on another man. (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 12)
    - "En cualquier lugar, en cualquier momento … con condón – Two naked men one wearing condom – b/w poster on foam core with photographer's signature. [11" x 17"] (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - "Rock Against AIDS Rock For Life" SFAF, Shanti & Mobilization Against AIDS, at the Farm [11" x 17"], 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - "A.I.D.S. In The Food Industry … Answers"-Black/Red on white graphic" co-sponsored by the Bay Area Womens Culinary Alliance and SFAF -at the Valencia Rose, [11" x 17"], October 8th (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - AIDS Foundation event at Hilton Hotel, SF- 5 b/w oversized contact sheets [11" x 14"] (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - "Dress for the Occasion." Naked man wearing a condom. Copyright 1988 San Francisco Aids Foundation (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - "Listo Parar accion ... con condon." B/W, two men, one wearing a condom, about to have sex. Copyright 1990 San Francisco Aids Foundation. Photo: Warwick May. (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 6)
    - "There's Strength in our Numbers" – two men (clothed) embracing" – San Francisco Stop AIDS Project 100% [14-5/8" x 20"] (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 7)
  - Los Angeles Area Posters (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - "Safe Sex …Are You Man Enough?" b/w poster, copyright B. Rapp. Aid for AIDS Core Program, LA. Accompanied by typed explanation by Kenneth D. Brock, M.S.W., [11" x 17"] (2 copies)., circa 1985; 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - "Charles Pierce as Mae West Says …" Aid for AIDS Program in Los Angeles, photo by Steve Speliotes, [11" x 17"] (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - "AIDS Education for the Deaf .. Everything You Want to Know About AIDS" – center in Van Nuys, CA, [10-1/2" x 13"] (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - "If You Don't Want to Get AIDS … One out of Every Seven People with L.A. has Used I.V. Drugs" copyright AIDS Project L.A., [11" x 17"], 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - "Let's Make It Safer To Play In L.A" – L.A. Cares., copyright Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center of L.A, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - The CARES Team -- California Dept. Health Services/GLCSC, copyright The Communication Works [11" x 17"] (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 6 - 9)
      - "Don't Forget Your Rubbers" (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - "Play Safely" (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - "Keep It Clean" (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - "Don't Play With Strangers" (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - "Fight the Fear with the Facts" – b/w photo poster, copyright AIDS Project L.A., [17" x 14"], 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - "Worried about Aids? Please Learn all the Facts." English & Cambodian language. Long Beach United Cambodian Community and AIDS research & Education project, California State University, Long Beach. Art by Salika - Funded by the California Department of Health Services. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - "Aids the Disease: Protect Yourself and Your Family." English & Cambodian Language. Long Beach United Cambodian Community and AIDS Research & Education project, California State University, Long Beach. Art by Salika - Funded by the California Department of Health Services (2 copies). (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 12)
    - "AIDS the Disease: A New Kind of Threat?" English & Cambodian language. Long Beach United Cambodian Community and AIDS research & Education project, California State University, Long Beach. Art by Salika - Funded by the California Department of Health Services. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 13)
  - "Kaposi's Sarcoma Research and Education Foundation" – mounted on multilayer base – Early AIDS information, early 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Shanti Foundation (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - " 1st Annual Lesbian & Gay Day at Candlestick: A Benefit for Shanti Project" – [11" x 17"], Saturday, September 14th, 1985 or 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - "AIDS Bike-a-thon … Cycle for Shanti" – Modified Poster, multicolor graphic [12-1/2" x 18-3/4"], May 9th, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - "Here's what people are saying about Shanti Project … We're here for you San Francisco!" – b/w with photographs and quotes – Ad copy [11-1/2" x 18"] (Box 4, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - "The Courage to Care … A Shanti Seminar for AIDS Health Care and Social Service Providers" – [11" x 17"], October 17-18, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - 1983 Loose Posters - California (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - "Bleachman" Poster, with multi-color graphic [11" x 14"], 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - "SIDA AIDS Llamenos … con Confianza" – SFAF, American Red Cross and Pacific Telesis Foundation [12" x 18"] (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - "Some People Think You Can Catch AIDS From A Glass …" SFAF, California Medical Association (CMA), AIDS Project Los Angeles (APLA) [11" x 17"] (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 3 - 4)
  - Rubberman (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - As An Honorary Rubberman pledge, b/w poster mounted, [11" x 17"] (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - "Rubbermen Want You" – Man with mustache, leather jacket, jeans, showing condom in pocket – Ad for models for the 1991 Ruberman Calander, b/w [8-1/2" x 14"], 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - "Be a Rubberman. Use a Condom every time." San Francisco AIDS Foundation, San Francisco Department of Public Health. (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Publications (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "Understanding AIDS: A Message from the Surgeon General" – BRAILLE edition – US Dept. of Health and Human Services, No. (CDC) HHS-88-8407, [10-1/2" x 12-1/1"], 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 1)
    - Leadership Recognition Dinner – brochure – SFAF, [5-1/2" x 12"], March 22, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 2)
    - The University Report - "Novel Approach Curbs Spread of AIDS" – The University of Washington, June 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 3)
    - "All For One / One For All: 1990 Annual Report" – San Francisco AIDS Foundation, in memory of Ron DeLuca, also contains the SFAF Mission Statement [9" x 14"], 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 4)
    - "1984 The Year of the Plague" – Selected Coverage from the San Francisco Chronicle, b/w newsprint magazine [11" x 14"], 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 5)
  - Other SF AIDS-related Ephemera (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - "Lighting The Way For Community Survival …SF Black Coalition on AIDS announces The Northern California African American Women HIV/AIDS Conference, [11" x 17"], May 3-4, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - "Ojos Que No Ven…" b/w envelope, Instituto Familiar de la Raza, Inc. of San Francisco/Adfinitum Films [9" x 12"] (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 2)
    - "AIDS Prevention Project … A Conference on AIDS Prevention/ San Francisco State University" [8-1/2" x 14"], November 11-16, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 3)
    - "AIDS Memorial Quilt Exhibit" – Photograph of section of quilt, Litrium Building [16-3/4" x 16"], December 1-4, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 4)
    - "Coming Home." b/w double-sided flyer for supportive services for lesbians and gay men facing life-threatening illness. San Francisco, CA (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 5)
    - "I Have AIDS Please Hug Me … I Can't Make You Sick" – child's drawing by J. Keeler, AIDS Hotline for Kids/Center for Attitudinal Healing, Tiburon, CA [11" x 15"], 1987 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 6)
    - " Tell your kids about AIDS now. Or someone else may have to later." AIDS. It's up to you. State of California AIDS Education Campaign. (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 7)
    - "Don't Listen to Rumors about AIDS. Get the Facts! - Patti Labelle" Close up of Patti Labelle. American Red Cross, Public Health Service, US Department of Health and Human Services. Photo: Lennon the Photographer. (2 copies). (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 8)
    - " UCSF AIDS History Project: Documenting the Epidemic." Flyer from an exhibition at UCSF. November 25, 2013 - June 1, 2014. Includes small label., 2013 - 2014 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 9)
  - Large Oversize Posters and Ephemera
    - French Language - France/French Canadian, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - "Un Homme et Une Femme... un condom?" Poster. French Language. Sante et Bien-etre social Canada (double sided)., ca 1990s. (Box 7, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - "Nutrition - HIV Infection: First International Conference". Color poster. French Language. Cannes, France. April 1995. (Box 7, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - "Prenez la chose en mains." Poster. D.D.A.S.S. De Haute Savoie. 1998. (Box 7, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - "Regardez la chose en face." Poster. French Language, 1998. (Box 7, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - "Education about Aids, a Right, a Responsibility. " France Unesco Headquarters, 1995. (Box 7, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - "Declaration of the Paris AIDS summit. " English, French, Spanish languages. International Council of AIDS service organizations. (Box 7, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - "Le SIDA en Europe. New Challenges for social and behavioral sciences – 2nd European Conference on the methods and results of social and behavioral research on AIDS. France, 1997., ca 1997. (Box 7, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - "Le SIDA ca peut vous arrive! Protegez vous." (double-sided, French and English language). Canada. (Box 7, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - "AIDS. It's time for schools to act." Unesco France, World AIDS Day, 1992. (2 copies/versions, one pink and one blue). (Box 7, Folder 1, Item 9)
      - "Sports divers mien faites pas trop assurez." France., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Portuguese Language (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - "10 Precaucoes para o laboratorio." Portuguese language. (laminated) (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - "10 recomendacoes para os profissionais de saude." Portuguese language. (laminated). (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - "Mulheres em movimento enfrentando a AIDS. Projecto araye, programa de prevencao para a comunidade Afro-Brasileira." Brasil, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - "Voce precisa aprender a transar com a existencia da AIDS." Brasil. (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - "Nao importa com quem." Brasil., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - English language: USA/English Canada (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - MSMGF – Global Forum on MSM & HIV, Annual Report. Pamphlet, 8 ½" x 11"., 2012 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - "Spirit of Sport – Rage against Roids." Canada. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - "Courage: It takes more than condoms to fight AIDS. It takes your acceptance & understanding." Canada/Canadian AIDS Society. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - "Statement of Belief." UNDP. HIV & Development Program. Senegal/USA Consultation., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - "Guiding Principles on HIV & AIDS." UNDP. HIV & Development Program. Senegal/USA Consultation, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - "Sexually Transmitted Diseases." Johns Hopkins College, USA. (Double-sided). (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - "Hablemos Entre Hombres." Spanish Language, USA. El Foro Hispano Sombre el SIDA, NYC. USA. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - "Taking care safely is good care." Canadian Public Health Association. (double-sided, English/French Language). Canada. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - "Family Planning Helps Everyone." Population Information Program, Johns Hopkins School of Public Health. USA, 1994., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - "AIDS: Sharing the Challenge." World AIDS day – Division of Education for the quality of life., ca December 1, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - "Men: Partners in Reproductive Health." Population reference bureau, Washington DC. USA. (Version 1.), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 11)
      - "Men: Partners in Reproductive Health." Population reference bureau, Washington DC. USA. (Version 2.), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - "Los Hombres: Companeros en la salud reproductive." Spanish language version of 7:11." Population reference bureau, Washington DC. USA, 1997. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 13)
      - "George Bush Sr. "Cerrar nuestra fronteras a aquellas con el virus (VIH) crea un clima de temor e ignorancia " ". Illustrated Presidential signature, Seal of the President of the United States. Act Up, USA. 1990s., ca 1990s. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 14)
      - "Take Pride in yourself; Take care of each other." AIDS Vancouver, Canada. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 15)
      - "Call Randy. The Safest Place to Meet the Man of your dreams is at a STOP AIDS Meeting." STOP AIDS Los Angeles. Department of Education of the Gay & Lesbian Community Service Center, Funded in part by the California Department of Health Services. (2 copies). (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 16)
      - "Hot, Horny and Healthy" b/w poster, copyright Black Gay & Lesbian Forum, [18" x 24"], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 17)
      - "This is the Way Many People Deal with HIV." Photographic poster of trio of people covering eyes, ears, and mouth. America Responds to AIDS. Department of Health & Human Services, Public Health Service, Centers for Disease Control. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 18)
      - "AIDSCOM: Education is Not Enough." Illustrated poster of the world map with people's faces in continents. AIDSCOM, Washington D.C. Art by Siquenza. Ca 1988. (2 copies)., ca 1998. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 19)
      - "Great Sex! Don't let AIDS Stop It." Poster Developed by Safer Sex Committee of NYC. Sticker from SFAF affixed to "find out more" box. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 20)
      - "Love AIDS People." Public Service campaign by Shoshin Society, Washington D.C. © 1988. (2 copies)., ca 1988. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 21)
      - "AIDS. A prenda e Viva. " Spanish Language. SPAL, Somerville, Massachussetts, USA. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 22)